(window.webpackJsonp=window.webpackJsonp||[]).push([[3],{200:function(e,a,t){"use strict";t.r(a);var n=t(0),i=t.n(n),o=t(203),r=t(206),s=[{interviewSet:1,questions:[{id:1,question:"What is html? 1",answer:"html is",example:"<a name=”topsection”>Top</a> <p> - - - - - - - - - - - - </p> <div> - - - - - - - - - - - - </div> <a href=”#topsection”>GO TO TOP</a> ",tip:"tip"},{id:2,question:"What are tags?",answer:"Most of the content of the HTML document is enclosed by starting and ending tags. Various types of tags are available in HTML to add text, image, audio, and video in the document. Each tag is declared by enclosing with less than symbol (<) and the greater than symbol (>). A slash symbol (/) is used in the closing tag. ",example:"\n<p>Hello World!</p>\n<hr/>\n<div>Hello World, again!</div>\n\nHere, three tags are declared which are p, br and div.\n",tip:"hr tag is one type of empty that is used to create a horizontal line in the HTML document. No ending tag is added for this tag and the starting tag is closed by a slash (/).  \n"},{id:3,question:"plm ? ",answer:"html is",example:'<img src="picture.gif" width="300" height="200"  usemap="#imgmap">\n\n<map name="imgmap">\n  \t<area shape="circle" coords="75,45,5" href="flower.htm" >\n \t<area shape="rect" coords="10,5,90,150" href="bird.htm" >\n</map>\n',tip:"tip"},{id:4,question:"da?",answer:"html is",example:"example",tip:"tip"},{id:5,question:"How do get nth Fibonacci number?",answer:"function fibonacci(n){\n  var fibo = [0, 1];\n  \n  if (n <= 2) return 1;\n\n  for (var i = 2; i <=n; i++ ){\n   fibo[i] = fibo[i-1]+fibo[i-2];\n  }\n\n return fibo[n];\n} \n\n> fibonacci(12);\n  = 144 ",tip:"tip",algorithm:!0,algorithmProblem:"function fibonacci(n){\n// Add your solution beyond this comment\n\n\n// Add your solution above this comment\n} \n\nfibonacci(12);",algorithmAnswer:144}]},{interviewSet:2,questions:[{id:1,question:"What is html? 2 - 1",answer:"html is",example:'<img src="picture.gif" width="300" height="200"  usemap="#imgmap">\n\n<map name="imgmap">\n  \t<area shape="circle" coords="75,45,5" href="flower.htm" >\n \t<area shape="rect" coords="10,5,90,150" href="bird.htm" >\n</map>\n',tip:"tip"},{id:2,question:"What are tags?",answer:"Most of the content of the HTML document is enclosed by starting and ending tags. Various types of tags are available in HTML to add text, image, audio, and video in the document. Each tag is declared by enclosing with less than symbol (<) and the greater than symbol (>). A slash symbol (/) is used in the closing tag. ",example:"\n<p>Hello World!</p>\n<hr/>\n<div>Hello World, again!</div>\n\nHere, three tags are declared which are p, br and div.\n",tip:"hr tag is one type of empty that is used to create a horizontal line in the HTML document. No ending tag is added for this tag and the starting tag is closed by a slash (/).  \n"},{id:3,question:"What is html? 2 - 2",answer:"html is",example:"<a name=”topsection”>Top</a> <p> - - - - - - - - - - - - </p> <div> - - - - - - - - - - - - </div> <a href=”#topsection”>GO TO TOP</a> ",tip:"tip"},{id:4,question:"What is html? 2 - 3",answer:"html is",example:'<img src="picture.gif" width="300" height="200"  usemap="#imgmap">\n\n<map name="imgmap">\n  \t<area shape="circle" coords="75,45,5" href="flower.htm" >\n \t<area shape="rect" coords="10,5,90,150" href="bird.htm" >\n</map>\n',tip:"tip"},{id:5,question:"How do get nth Fibonacci number?",answer:"function fibonacci(n){\n  var fibo = [0, 1];\n  \n  if (n <= 2) return 1;\n\n  for (var i = 2; i <=n; i++ ){\n   fibo[i] = fibo[i-1]+fibo[i-2];\n  }\n\n return fibo[n];\n} \n\n> fibonacci(12);\n  = 144 ",tip:"tip",algorithm:!0,algorithmProblem:"function fibonacci(n){\n// Add your solution beyond this comment\n\n\n// Add your solution above this comment\n} \n\nfibonacci(12);",algorithmAnswer:144}]},{interviewSet:3,questions:[{id:1,question:"What is html? 3 - 1",answer:"html is",example:"<a name=”topsection”>Top</a> <p> - - - - - - - - - - - - </p> <div> - - - - - - - - - - - - </div> <a href=”#topsection”>GO TO TOP</a> ",tip:"tip"},{id:2,question:"What are tags?",answer:"Most of the content of the HTML document is enclosed by starting and ending tags. Various types of tags are available in HTML to add text, image, audio, and video in the document. Each tag is declared by enclosing with less than symbol (<) and the greater than symbol (>). A slash symbol (/) is used in the closing tag. ",example:"\n<p>Hello World!</p>\n<hr/>\n<div>Hello World, again!</div>\n\nHere, three tags are declared which are p, br and div.\n",tip:"hr tag is one type of empty that is used to create a horizontal line in the HTML document. No ending tag is added for this tag and the starting tag is closed by a slash (/).  \n"},{id:3,question:"What is html? 3 - 3",answer:"html is",example:'<img src="picture.gif" width="300" height="200"  usemap="#imgmap">\n\n<map name="imgmap">\n  \t<area shape="circle" coords="75,45,5" href="flower.htm" >\n \t<area shape="rect" coords="10,5,90,150" href="bird.htm" >\n</map>\n',tip:"tip"},{id:4,question:"What is html? 3 - 4",answer:"html is",example:"example",tip:"tip"},{id:5,question:"How do get nth Fibonacci number?",answer:"I create an array and start from iterate through.",example:"function fibonacci(n){\n  var fibo = [0, 1];\n  \n  if (n <= 2) return 1;\n\n  for (var i = 2; i <=n; i++ ){\n   fibo[i] = fibo[i-1]+fibo[i-2];\n  }\n\n return fibo[n];\n} \n\n> fibonacci(12);\n  = 144 ",tip:"tip",algorithm:!0,algorithmProblem:"function fibonacci(n){\n// Add your solution beyond this comment\n\n\n// Add your solution above this comment\n} \n\nfibonacci(12);",algorithmAnswer:144}]}],l=t(453),c=t(451);var m=function(e){var a,t;function n(){for(var a,t=arguments.length,n=new Array(t),i=0;i<t;i++)n[i]=arguments[i];return(a=e.call.apply(e,[this].concat(n))||this).state={doneQuizData:[],userAnswers:[],userExamples:[],done:!1},a.getQuizSet=function(){var e=s[Math.floor(Math.random()*s.length)];Object(o.b)("/quiz/",{state:{interviewData:e}})},a}t=e,(a=n).prototype=Object.create(t.prototype),a.prototype.constructor=a,a.__proto__=t;var m=n.prototype;return m.componentDidMount=function(){var e=this;void 0!==this.props.location.state.done&&this.setState(function(){return{doneQuizData:e.props.location.state.doneQuizData,userAnswers:e.props.location.state.userAnswers,userExamples:e.props.location.state.userExamples,done:e.props.location.state.done}})},m.render=function(){var e=this.state.userAnswers,a=this.state.userExamples;return i.a.createElement(r.a,null,i.a.createElement("div",{className:"container"},i.a.createElement(o.a,{to:"/"},"Home"),i.a.createElement("div",{onClick:this.getQuizSet},"START"),!0===this.state.done&&i.a.createElement(i.a.Fragment,null,this.state.doneQuizData.map(function(t,n){return i.a.createElement("div",{key:n},i.a.createElement("div",{className:"row"},i.a.createElement("div",{className:"col-sm-12"},t.question)),i.a.createElement("div",{className:"row"},i.a.createElement("div",{className:"col-md-6"},i.a.createElement("div",{className:"preview-answer"},e[t.id]),a[t.id]&&i.a.createElement(l.a,{language:"javascript",style:c.a,showLineNumbers:!0,lineNumberStyle:{color:"#ff704d"}},a[t.id])),i.a.createElement("div",{className:"col-md-6"},i.a.createElement("div",{className:"preview-answer"},t.answer),t.example&&i.a.createElement(l.a,{language:"javascript",style:c.a,showLineNumbers:!0,lineNumberStyle:{color:"#ff704d"}},t.example),i.a.createElement("div",{className:"preview-answer"},t.tip))))}))))},n}(i.a.Component);a.default=m},202:function(e,a,t){var n;e.exports=(n=t(204))&&n.default||n},203:function(e,a,t){"use strict";var n=t(0),i=t.n(n),o=t(77),r=t.n(o);t.d(a,"a",function(){return r.a}),t.d(a,"b",function(){return o.navigate});t(202),t(10).default.enqueue,i.a.createContext({})},204:function(e,a,t){"use strict";t.r(a);t(22);var n=t(0),i=t.n(n),o=t(107);a.default=function(e){var a=e.location,t=e.pageResources;return t?i.a.createElement(o.a,Object.assign({location:a,pageResources:t},t.json)):null}},206:function(e,a,t){"use strict";var n=t(0),i=t.n(n),o=t(203),r=function(){return i.a.createElement("nav",{className:"navbar navbar-expand-md navbar-light navigation-color start-nav"},i.a.createElement("div",{className:"container"},i.a.createElement(o.a,{to:"/",className:"navbar-brand"},"Navbar"),i.a.createElement("button",{className:"navbar-toggler",type:"button","data-toggle":"collapse","data-target":"#navbarNavAltMarkup","aria-controls":"navbarNavAltMarkup","aria-expanded":"false","aria-label":"Toggle navigation"},i.a.createElement("span",{className:"navbar-toggler-icon"})),i.a.createElement("div",{className:"collapse navbar-collapse justify-content-md-end",id:"navbarNavAltMarkup"},i.a.createElement("div",{className:"navbar-nav text-right"},i.a.createElement(o.a,{className:"nav-item nav-link",href:"#"},"Interview Quiz"),i.a.createElement(o.a,{className:"nav-item nav-link",href:"#"},"About"),i.a.createElement("a",{className:"nav-item nav-link",href:"www.amazon.com",target:"_blank"},"Shop")))))};t.e(0).then(t.t.bind(null,201,7));a.a=function(e){var a=e.children;return i.a.createElement(i.a.Fragment,null,i.a.createElement(r,null),a)}}}]);
//# sourceMappingURL=component---src-pages-interview-quiz-js-8f4f3f26d1d376afee18.js.map